TOOL SHORT · DUMPS A short dump at 03:12.
Nobody wants to open ST22.
dumps user=DEVELOPER · today
dumpDetails CX_SY_REF_IS_INITIAL
getObjectSource zcl_order_service · line 142
terminatedAt · GET_DATA line 142 · stack read
Runtime error CX_SY_REF_IS_INITIAL Cause mo_config not bound at ->get( ) " line 141 + IF mo_config IS NOT BOUND. + mo_config = zcl_config=>get_instance( ). + ENDIF.
Cause, line and fix in one answer.
resolveTransport ZORDERS → DEVK900123
editObjectSource line 141 · activate=true
unitTestRun ZCL_ORDER_SERVICE
objectDiff active vs. previous
locked · written · activated · unlocked
ABAP Unit 3 passed · 0 failed Transport DEVK900123 Diff +3 lines · 0 removed
Fixed before the standup.
Dumps, read.
Cause, line, fix, activation and tests in one chat.
dumps dumpDetails editObjectSource
unitTestRun
github.com/williansaez/abap-adt-mcp